{
    "id": "1ad164ae41d842c8bad77bb7c792e062",
    "title": "Indefinite Pronouns Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b79223c4477e401a8e92fddbe7e1b8d3",
            "title": "Indefinite Personal Pronouns",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "................................. can't learn a new language in a week.",
                    "description": "We can use one or you to talk about people in general. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "You",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. should never tolerate injustice.",
                    "description": "We use one to talk about people in general including the speaker and the hearer. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "Somebody",
                        "Anybody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ..................................... get to Calicut?",
                    "description": "One is more formal than you however, both one and you can be used to talk about people in general. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "does one",
                        "do you",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... can find lots of people who speak English in India.",
                    "description": "We use one to talk about people in general including the speaker and the hearer. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "They",
                        "Somebody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................. knocked at the door.",
                    "description": "One is only used in general statements. In other cases, we use other pronouns like somebody or they. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "Anybody",
                        "Somebody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ do not allow smoking in the kitchen.",
                    "description": "One cannot be used when the meaning is not 'people in general'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "They",
                        "Somebody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Centuries ago ................................. believed that the sun went around the earth.",
                    "description": "One cannot be used to generalize about people who could not include the speaker you cannot be used to generalize about people who could not include the listener. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "one",
                        "you",
                        "they"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ should knock before walking into somebody's room.",
                    "description": "We use one and you to talk about people in general including the speaker and the hearer. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "You",
                        "One",
                        "They"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "One should never hide anything from ................................... doctor or lawyer.",
                    "description": "In American English, he, him and his can be used to refer back to one. This is not normal in British English. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "his",
                        "one's",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................ say her marriage is in trouble.",
                    "description": "They say = people say. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "They say",
                        "One says",
                        "You say"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................... doesn't know what to do in such situations.",
                    "description": "We use one to talk about people in general including the speaker and the hearer. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "One",
                        "Somebody",
                        "Anybody"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "...................................... going to widen the road.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "One is",
                        "You are",
                        "They are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}